Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1986-088
  - Center for Advanced Study of Behavioral Science, 1983; AD 12.14.7/16 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/16)
  - Facilities Planning, 9/1982-8/1983; PAD 12.14.7/29 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14.7/29)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 9/1982-9/1983; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/64)
  - Quad (Space), 1981-1983; AD 12.14.7/55 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/55)
  - Facilities and Planning, 9/1982-8/1983; AD 12.14.8/29 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.8/29)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 9/1981-8/1983; PAD 13.9 (Box 8, Folder PAD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library (including secondary letters), 9/1983-12/1983; PAD 13.9 (Box 8, Folder PAD 13.9)
  - Nuclear War Symposium-New York and Washington, 30620; AD 12.10.1 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Computer Science Advisory Committee, 9/78-3/1983; AD 13.10.5/1 (Box 8, Folder AD 13.10.5/1)
  - Computer Science Advisory Committee, 1982-1983; AD 13.10.5/1 (Box 8, Folder AD 13.10.5/1)
  - Visiting Committees (includes Report, "Advisory Boards and Visiting Committees at SU, Harvard, MIT..." by J. Lane, May 1982), 1982-1984; AD 13.10.5 (Box 8, Folder AD 13.10.5)
  - Law School Board of Visitors, 1983; AD 13.10.5/5 (Box 8, Folder AD 13.10.5/5)
  - Alumni Assoc. Board, 12/1981-5/1983; AL 3.1 (Box 9, Folder AL 3.1)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/1982-11/1982; B 1 (Box 9, Folder B 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 12/1982-2/1983; B 1 (Box 9, Folder B 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 3/1983-8/1983; B 1 (Box 9, Folder B 1)
  - Board of Trustees Budget Committee, B 14.1 (Box 9, Folder B 14.1)
  - Board of Trustees Investment Committee, 9/1982-8/1983; B 14.5 (Box 9, Folder B 14.5)
  - Board of Trustees Investment Committee, 3/1983-5/1983; B 14.5 (Box 9, Folder B 14.5)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Medical Center, 2/1982-11/1983; B 14.9 (Box 9, Folder B 14.9)
  - Academic Council, 1980-1981; C 1 (Box 9, Folder C 1)
  - Advisory Board, 9/1982-8/1983; C 3 (Box 9, Folder C 3)
  - Steering Committee, 1983; C 4.1 (Box 9, Folder C 4.1)
  - Committee on Committees, 6/1982-8/1983; C 4.2 (Box 9, Folder C 4.2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 9/1982-8/1983; C 5.7 (Box 9, Folder C 5.7)
  - Cabinet of Undergraduate Education, 9/1982-8/1983; C 5.7.1 (Box 9, Folder C 5.7.1)
  - Committee on Land, Building and Development, 9/1982-/1983; C 6 (Box 9, Folder C 6)
  - Committee on Investment Responsibility, 9/1982-8/8; C 7.7 (Box 9, Folder C 7.7)
  - Univ. Advisory Com.-Budget Plan., 9/1981-8/1983; C 7.13 (Box 9, Folder C 7.13)
  - Comm. on Parking and Transportation, 9/1982-8/8; C 8.1 (Box 9, Folder C 8.1)
  - Panel-Human Subject/Behavioral Science, 1982-83; C 8.9 (Box 9, Folder C 8.9)
  - US Government Relations-SU, 2/1983-8/1983; G 3 (Box 9, Folder G 3)
  - Federal Legislation, 9/1982-8/1983; G 3.1 (Box 9, Folder G 3.1)
  - Inter. Traffic in Arms Regulation, 9/1981-1/1982; G 3.7.6 (Box 9, Folder G 3.7.6)
  - EDUCOM, 11/1982-10/1983; G 3.10.12 (Box 9, Folder G 3.10.12)
  - Ad Hoc and Misc. Organizations, 9/1982-8/1983; O 1 (Box 10, Folder O 1)
  - Health Education Institute (HEI), 5/1981-6/1982; O 2.1 (Box 10, Folder O 2.1)
  - Consortium Finan. Higher Ed., 1980, 4/1982-8/1983; O 3.1 (Box 10, Folder O 3.1)
  - Consortium Finan. Higher Ed., 9/1982-8/1983; O 3.1 (Box 10, Folder O 3.1)
  - American Council on Education, 9/1982-8/1983; O 3.8 (Box 10, Folder O 3.8)
  - National Academy of Science, 1979-1983; O 3.42 (Box 10, Folder O 3.42)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 1981; O 8 (Box 10, Folder O 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 8/1982-12/1983; O 8 (Box 10, Folder O 8)
  - Association of American Universities, 1982-9/1983; O 8.7 (Box 10, Folder O 8.7)
  - Harvard University, 9/1981-8/1983; O 8.23 (Box 10, Folder O 8.23)
  - Eight Universities, 1979-1983; O 8.39 (Box 10, Folder O 8.39)
  - Stanford Synchrotron Radiation Lab, 9/1981-8/1983; R 1.9 (Box 10, Folder R 1.9)
  - Indirect costs, 2/1982-2/1983; R 3.1 (Box 10, Folder R 3.1)
  - Indirect costs, 1982-12/1983; R 3.1 (Box 10, Folder R 3.1)
  - Indirect costs, 1980-12/1981; R 3.1 (Box 10, Folder R 3.1)
  - Research Proposals, Misc. (Whitehead Institute, MIT), 1980-1983; R 4 (Box 10, Folder R 4)
  - Division of Laboratory Animal Med., 1981-82; R 1.14 (Box 10, Folder R 1.14)
  - Division of Laboratory Animal Med., 1/1982-12/1983; R 1.14 (Box 10, Folder R 1.14)
  - Students, General, 30475; ST 1 (Box 11, Folder ST 1)
  - ASSU, General, 5/80-8/1983; ST 2 (Box 11, Folder ST 2)
  - Stanford Band, 9/1981-8/1983; ST 3.4 (Box 11, Folder ST 3.4)
  - Black Student Union, 1980-8/1983; ST 3.6 (Box 11, Folder ST 3.6)
  - Gay and Lesbian Student (GLAS), 1/1983-8/1983; ST 4.2 (Box 11, Folder ST 4.2)
  - Chron files-President Kennedy (12 folders), 30328 (Box 12)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1987-063
  - Administrative Council, 12/72-1/1979; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 1/84-6/1984; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 7/84-12/1984; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 8/84-7/1984; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 5/84-7/1984; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 8/84-10/1984; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - General Correspondence A-H, 12/84-12/1985; AD 4.20 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20)
  - General Correspondence I-Z, 11/85-12/1984; AD 4.20 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20)
  - General Correspondence, 1/83-12/1983; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - General Correspondence, 1/84-12/1984; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, 9/82-9/1985; AD 11.6 (Box 2, Folder AD 11.6)
  - Budgets, 2/84 -8/1985; PAD 12.5 (Box 2, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 9/83-11/1984; PAD 12.5 (Box 2, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Office of Development, 9/83-8/1984; AD 12.10.1 (Box 2, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - AAU/ACE/NASULGC Joint Committee on Health Policy, 11/83-12/1984; AD 12.10.1 (Box 2, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Business Higher Education Forum, 1/84-12/1985; AD 12.10.1 (Box 2, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - DoD/University Forum, 2/82-10/1982; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - " ", 11/82-7/1983; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - " ", 7/83-12/1983; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - " ", 1/84-2/1984; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Joint Retreat: Fallen Leaf Lake, 30926; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - LNH A Personal Chronical of the Medical Reform Leg. AB799 and SB2012, 30225; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - New York Event, 6/82-6/1984; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Prospecting Program, 1982-84; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Visiting Committees Miscellaneous, 30103; AD 13.10.5 (Box 3, Folder AD 13.10.5)
  - Academic Computing and Info. Systems, 29342; AA 1.4.1 (Box 4, Folder AA 1.4.1)
  - Deans Council Agendas, 6/72-8/73; AA 1.5.1 (Box 4, Folder AA 1.5.1)
  - Athletics, Physical Ed. and Recreation, 9/83-8/1984; AA 4.1.30 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - School of Engineering, 9/83-12/1984; PAA 4.4 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.4)
  - School of Education, 7/83-8/1983; AA 4.5 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.5)
  - School of Education, 31382; PAA 4.5 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.5)
  - Stanford Medical School, 9/83-3/1984; PAA 4.6 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - Stanford Medical School, 11/83-12/1984; PAA 4.6 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - Hoover institution, General, 9/83-8/1984; AA 4.9 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Stanford Libraries, 9/83-8/1984; PAA 4.12 (Box 4, Folder PAA 4.12)
  - Assoc. Provost for Computing/Computer Forum, 30256; AA 4.16.1 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.16.1)
  - Stanford Univ. Medical Center, 9/83-12/1983; AA 4.17 (Box 4, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Univ. Medical Center, 1/84-3/1984; AA 4.17 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Univ. Medical Center, 4/84-8/1984; AA 4.17 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Univ. Medical Center, 9/84-8/1985; AA 4.17 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Univ. Medical Center, 2/84-8/1985; PAA 4.17 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.17)
  - Stanford Univ. Hosp. Board of Directors, 9/83-8/1984; AA 4.17.2 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - Hospital Modernization Project, 9/83-8/1984; AA 4.17.5 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.17.5)
  - Advisory Committee on Computing Science and Computing, 30376; AA 4.22 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.22)
  - Board of Trustees, Miscellaneous, 9/84-8/1985; B1 (Box 5, Folder B1)
  - Board of Trustees, Miscellaneous, 9/1983- 8/1984; B1 (Box 5, Folder B1)
  - Calif. Postsecondary Ed. Commission, 11/84-12/1982; G1.3.5 (Box 5, Folder G1.3.5)
  - Federal Legislation, 9/83-8/1984; G3.1 (Box 6, Folder G3.1)
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 9/83-8/1984; ST 1 (Box 6, Folder ST 1)
  - Assoc. Students of Stanford Univ., 30560; ST 2 (Box 6, Folder ST 2)
  - You Can Make a Difference Conference, 30713; ST 3.29/3 (Box 6, Folder ST 3.29/3)
  - World Affairs Council, 12/82-9/1986; 1.31 (Box 6, Folder 1.31)
  - Pacific-Ten Conference (Pac Ten), 30682; 3.47 (Box 6, Folder 3.47)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 6/84-8/1985; 8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 9/83-8/1984; 8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Association of American Universities, 30956; 8.7 (Box 6, Folder 8.7)
  - Animal Research, 3/83-12/1983; R1.14 (Box 6, Folder R1.14)
  - Indirect Costs, 1/83-8/1984; R3.1 (Box 7, Folder R3.1)
  - Indirect Costs, 9/83-8/1984; R3.1 (Box 7, Folder R3.1)
  - Advisory Board, 9/83-7/1983; C3 (Box 7, Folder C3)
  - Steering Committee, 9/83-8/1984; C4.1 (Box 7, Folder C4.1)
  - Steering Committee, 9/84-12/1984; C4.1 (Box 7, Folder C4.1)
  - Steering Committee, 1/85-8/1985; C4.1 (Box 7, Folder C4.1)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 9/82-8/1986; C5.3 (Box 7, Folder C5.3)
  - Education and Employment of Women in the universities, 11/73-5/1980; C6.4 (Box 7, Folder C6.4)
  - Committee on Land and Building Devel., 9/83-8/1984; C6.6 (Box 7, Folder C6.6)
  - Faculty Affirmative Action Committee, 1/80-1/1983; C6.10 (Box 7, Folder C6.10)
  - Commission on Investment Responsibility, 9/83-9/1984; C7.7 (Box 7, Folder C7.7)
  - Commission on Investment Responsibility, 9/84-8/1985; C7.7 (Box 7, Folder C7.7)
  - University Advisory Commission on Budget Planning, 9/72-3/1984; C7.13 (Box 7, Folder C7.13)
  - Administrative Panel on External Affirmative Action, 1/74-10/1981; C8.13 (Box 7, Folder C8.13)
  - SLAC/SSRL Correspondence, 1/85-12/1985; C9.4 (Box 7, Folder C9.4)
  - Administrative Panel on Privacy of Information, 8/73-1/8; C11 (Box 7, Folder C11)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1987-064
  - General Correspondence, 1/85-8/1986; AD 4.20 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Condolence Letters, 10/85-12/1986; AD 4.20.2 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20.2)
  - General/Accepted Invitations, 1/86-10/1986; AD 4.20.4 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20.4)
  - Nonsense, 9/85-8/1986; AD 4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters, 11/85-12/1986; AD 4.20.6 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.20.6)
  - Admissions Office, 12/82-8/1986; AD 8.1 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.1)
  - Admissions Office, 2/83-8/1986; PAD 8.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.1)
  - Admissions Cases, 9/85-8/1986; AD 8.1.2 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - Admissions Office, 6/84-9/1985; AD 8.1.2 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 9/84-8/1986; AD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 9/83-8/1984; AD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 2/85-8/1986; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 9/83-8/1984; PAD 8.18 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/85-8/1986; AD 9.6 (Box 2, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/83-8/1985; AD 9.6 (Box 2, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/85-8/1986; PAD 9.6 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 4/80-8/1985; PAD 9.6 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/83-8/1984; PAD 9.6 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.6)
  - United Stanford Employees (USE), 9/84-8/1985; AD 10.7.8 (Box 2, Folder AD 10.7.8)
  - United Stanford Employees (USE), 9/83-8/1984; AD 10.7.8 (Box 2, Folder AD 10.7.8)
  - Grievance Cases, 9/84-8/1985; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 2, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievance Cases, 9/83-8/1984; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 2, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Salaries, 9/85-8/1986; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.19)
  - Salaries, 9/83-8/1985; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.19)
  - Stanford University Press, 9/85-11/1986; PAD 11.8.9 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.8.9)
  - Stanford University Press, 9/82-8/1985; PAD 11.8.9 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.8.9)
  - Stanford Investment Management Office (SIMO), 1/84-6/1984; AD 12.3.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.3.1)
  - Stanford Investment Management Office (SIMO), 9/83-12/1983; AD 12.3.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.3.1)
  - Stanford Investment Management Office (SIMO), 10/82-8/1985; PAD 12.3.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.3.1)
  - Budgets, 1/85-5/1986; AD 12.5 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 6/83-12/1984; AD 12.5 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 1/86-8/1986; PAD 12.5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 9/85-12/1985; PAD 12.5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Office of Development, 9/85-8/1986; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/84-8/1985; AD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/85-8/1986; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/84-8/1985; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/83-8/1984; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Medical Center Fundraising, 8/84-9/1985; AD 12.10.3 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3)
  - Medical Center Fundraising, 8/82-8/1984; AD 12.10.3 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3)
  - Gifts Miscellaneous, 1/84-8/1986; AD 12.10.3/5-1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-1)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 8/83-8/1986; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Carnegie Commission on Education and Economic Progress (Hamburg, etc), 2/84-4/1984; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Foundations Miscellaneous, 9/85-8/1986; AD 12.10.4 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Foundations Miscellaneous, 8/85-9/1985; AD 12.10.4 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Foundations Miscellaneous, 9/83-8/1985; PAD 12.10.4 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4)
  - Keck Fund/Trust, 9/82-8/1986; AD 12.10.4/6 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.4/6)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 9/82-8/1986; AD 12.10.4/67 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.4/67)
  - Markey, Lucille P., Charitable Trust, 8/85-8/1986; AD 12.10.4/131 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.4/131)
  - Technology Licensing/Patents/Copyrights, 1/84-8/1986; AD 12.11 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.11)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/83-8/1986; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Memorial Church (Space), 12/82 -; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14.7/50)
  - Academic Computing and Information Systems, 9/83-8/1986; AA 1.4.1 (Box 5, Folder AA 1.4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/83 -; AA 4.1 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/85 -; PAA 4.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/84 -; PAA 4.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/83 -; PAA 4.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, 9/83-8/1986; AA 4.1.12 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.1.12)
  - Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 9/85-8/1986; AA 4.1.30 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 9/84-8/1985; AA 4.1.30 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 9/83-8/1986; PAA 4.1.30 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.30)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/85-8/1986; AA 4.2 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/81-8/1985; AA 4.2 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/85-8/1986; PAA 4.2 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/83-8/1985; PAA 4.2 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/81-8/1985; PAA 4.2 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.2)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 9/82-8/1985; PAA 4.3 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.3)
  - School of Education, 8/85-8/1986; AA 4.5 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.5)
  - School of Education, 9/82-8/1985; AA 4.5 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.5)
  - School of Education, 9/85-8/1986; PAA 4.5 (Box 7, Folder PAA 4.5)
  - School of Education, 9/84-8/1985; PAA 4.5 (Box 7, Folder PAA 4.5)
  - School of Education, 9/83-8/1984; PAA 4.5 (Box 7, Folder PAA 4.5)
  - School of Medicine, 9/85-8/1986; AA 4.6 (Box 7, Folder AA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 9/84-8/1985; AA 4.6 (Box 7, Folder AA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 9/85-8/1986; PAA 4.6 (Box 7, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 1/85-6/1985; PAA 4.6 (Box 7, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/84-8/1985; AA 4.9 (Box 7, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Hoover Institution, 3/85-6/1985; PAA 4.9 (Box 8, Folder PAA 4.9)
  - Hoover Institution, 1/84-8/1985; PAA 4 9 (Box 8, Folder PAA 4 9)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/82-8/1983; PAA 4.9 (Box 8, Folder PAA 4.9)
  - Stanford Libraries, 9/84-8/1986; AA 4.12 (Box 8, Folder AA 4.12)
  - Stanford Libraries, 9/83-8/1984; AA 4.12 (Box 8, Folder AA 4.12)
  - Stanford Libraries, 9/85-8/1986; PAA 4.12 (Box 8, Folder PAA 4.12)
  - Stanford Libraries, 9/84-8/1985; PAA 4.12 (Box 8, Folder PAA 4.12)
  - Research Libraries Group, 1/83-10/1986; AA 4.12.1 (Box 8, Folder AA 4.12.1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 9/83-7/1986; AA 4.13 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.13)
  - School of Law, 9/81-8/1986; AA 4.15 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.15)
  - Stanford University Medical Center, 9/85-8/1986; AA 4.17 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford University Medical Center/ Hospital/Blood Bank (Fact Book), 1984-85; AA 4.17 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford University Hospital Board of Directors, 9/85-8/1986; AA 4.17.2 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - Stanford University Hospital Board of Directors, 2/85-8/1985; AA 4.17.2 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - Hospital Modernization Project, 9/84-8/1985; AA 4.17.5 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.17.5)
  - Center for Molecular and Genetic Medicine, 7/84-8/1985; AA 4.18 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.18)
  - Center for Molecular and Genetic Medicine, 9/85-8/1986; AA 4.18 (Box 9, Folder AA 4.18)
  - Alumni Association, 9/85-8/1986; AL 3 (Box 10, Folder AL 3)
  - Alumni Association, 9/84-8/1985; AL 3 (Box 10, Folder AL 3)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/85-8/1985; B 1 (Box 10, Folder B 1)
  - Academic Council: Minutes/Reports, 9/83-8/1985; C 1 (Box 10, Folder C 1)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 5/83-8/1985; C 2 (Box 10, Folder C 2)
  - Steering Committee (StC), 9/85-8/1986; C 4.1 (Box 10, Folder C 4.1)
  - Committee on Committees (CoC), 9/83-8/1984; C 4.2 (Box 10, Folder C 4.2)
  - Committee on Lands and Buildings, 9/85-8/1986; C 6.6 (Box 10, Folder C 6.6)
  - Sub-Committee on Real Estate, 31048; C 6.6.4 (Box 11, Folder C 6.6.4)
  - Commission on Investment, 9/85-12/1986; C 7.7 (Box 11, Folder C 7.7)
  - Federal Legislation, 9/85-8/1986; G 3.1 (Box 11, Folder G 3.1)
  - Federal Legislation, 9/84-8/1985; G 3.1 (Box 11, Folder G 3.1)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 8/83-11/1985; O 3.43 (Box 11, Folder O 3.43)
  - National Collegiate Athletic, 9/82-8/1985; O 3.44 (Box 11, Folder O 3.44)
  - Pacific-10 Conference, 9/85-8/1986; O 3.47 (Box 11, Folder O 3.47)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 1/86-8/1986; O 8 (Box 12, Folder O 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 1/86-8/1986; O 8 (Box 12, Folder O 8)
  - Report, Johns Hopkins, 31564; O 8 (Box 12, Folder O 8)
  - Association of American Universities, 10/83-8/1986; O 8.7 (Box 12, Folder O 8.7)
  - Association of American Universities, 2/85-11/1985; O 8.7 (Box 12, Folder O 8.7)
  - Animal Research, 1985; R 1.4 (Box 12, Folder R 1.4)
  - Animal Research, 1984; R 1.4 (Box 12, Folder R 1.4)
  - Indirect Cost (Research), 9/85-8/1986; R 3.1 (Box 12, Folder R 3.1)
  - Indirect Cost (Research), 9/84-8/1985; R 3.1 (Box 13, Folder R 3.1)
  - Indirect Cost (Research), 12/83-7/1984; R 3.1 (Box 13, Folder R 3.1)
  - Students Miscellaneous, 9/85-8/1986; ST 1 (Box 13, Folder ST 1)
  - Students Miscellaneous, 8/84-8/1985; ST 1 (Box 13, Folder ST 1)
  - Public Service Center, 9/85-8/1986; ST 3.29 (Box 13, Folder ST 3.29)
  - Clean Sites Incorporated (5 folders), 1985 (Box 13)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1988-086
  - Administrative Council, 2/85-8/1986; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 9/86-8/1987; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 6/85-8/1985; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 1/85-5/1985; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 9/85-12/1985; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 1/86-5/1986; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 6/86-8/1986; PAD 4.12 (Box 2, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 4.12 (Box 2, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 9/86-8/1987; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Condolence Letters, 1/87-7/88; AD 4.20.2 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.2)
  - Congratulation letters, 7/84-8/1985; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.3)
  - Congratulation letters, 9/85-8/1986; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.3)
  - General/Acceptance Invitations, 3/87-7/88; AD 4.20.4 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.4)
  - Nonsense Letters, 1/87-1/88; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Nonsense Letters, 2/88-7/88; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Routine Recommendations, 1/87-6/88; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.20.6)
  - Admissions Cases, 9/86-8/1987; AD 8.1.2 (Box 3, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - SU in Washington D.C., 8/82-5/1986; AD 8.10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 8.10.1)
  - Housing Faculty, Staff, 9/86-5/1987; AD 8.18 (Box 3, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Chicano Affairs, 9/83-8/1984; PAD 9.2 (Box 3, Folder PAD 9.2)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/86-6/1987; AD 9.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 9.6 (Box 3, Folder PAD 9.6)
  - Employment Inquiries, 9/85-8/1986; AD 10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.1)
  - Employment Inquiries, 9/86-8/1987; AD 10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.1)
  - Grievance Cases, 9/85-8/1986; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Stanford Invest. Management Office, 3/85-6/1987; AD 12.3.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.3.1)
  - Budget Facilities, 9/86-6/1987; AD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budget Facilities, 1985; AD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budget Facilities, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Office of Development, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Medical Center Fundraising, 9/85-8/1987; AD 12.10.3 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Hewlett Foundation, 9/82-8/1986; AD 12.10.3/5-29 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-29)
  - David Packard Foundation, 9/82-6/1986; AD 12.10.3/5-38 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-38)
  - Miscellaneous Foundations, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.10.4 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - William Keck Trust, 9/86-6/1987; AD 12.10.4/6 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.4/6)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.10.4/67 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.4/67)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Near West Campus, 6/84-8/1986; AD 12.14.7/31 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14.7/31)
  - Corporate Support Near West, 31503; AD 12.14.7/31 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14.7/31)
  - Near West Campus, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.14.7/31 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14.7/31)
  - Near West Campus, 5/83-8/1985; PAD 12.14.7/31 (Box 5, Folder PAD 12.14.7/31)
  - Memorial Church Space, 9/86-8/1987; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.14.7/50)
  - Graduate Division, 1977-8/1986; PAA 1.13 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.13)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/86-8/1987; AA 4.1 (Box 5, Folder AA 4.1)
  - Humanities Center, 10/82-8/1985; PAA 4.1.1/2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1.1/2)
  - Department of Athletics, 9/86-8/1987; AA 4.1.30 (Box 6, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Department of Athletics, 9/86-8/1987; PAA 4.1.30 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.30)